http://www.speakwellbeing.com/privacy-policy/

Planning for a Virtual Event? You're in the Right Place! Search for Virtual Event Types.
Call Today: 503-699-5031
Privacy Policy
AS A CONDITION OF YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY. This website is operated by copyright holder. (referred to as “Company,” “us,” “we,” and “our”). We are committed to respecting your privacy and we have created this privacy policy to explain how we use the information that we collect through your use of this Website. Please read this policy and familiarize yourself with its content as it will govern your use of this site.
YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OF AGE TO USE THIS WEBSITE.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may track the Internet Protocol (IP) address which you use to visit this website and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you voluntarily provide us with your personally identifiable information. We may use and share this anonymous data for any purpose including sharing statistical information with current and potential advertisers.
Cookies: We may use cookies on our site in order to improve your browsing experience by personalizing your experience on our site, providing a streamlined sign-up and login process, determining which portions of our site are visited and tailoring advertising to best serve your needs. Cookies may be placed by an outside company that performs tracking and statistical analysis of visitor behavior pattern, please note that we have no control over third parties and their business practices.
Collection, Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information: We may collect, use and share your personally identifiable information for any lawful purpose.
To access some areas of this website you must first register; such registration will require you to provide personally identifying information. Whether or not you choose to provide the information we request is entirely up to you. If you choose not to provide the information which we request, you may be unable to access certain areas of this website or obtain the coupons offered by our site.
If you choose to provide information to us through our online registration, you may be asked to provide your personal information that may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other identifying information. We may share the personal information which you provide with our third party processing agents, affiliates and advertisers.
We may use the personal information which you provide to send you information, either online or offline, via email, direct mail, SMS text messaging and telemarketing, regarding products or services offered by third-party advertisers. In addition, we reserve the right to rent, sell or share the personal information which you provide with unaffiliated third-parties; these third-parties may use this information for online and offline marketing purposes.
By signing up on our website and providing your personal information you are expressly consenting to receive communications from us and from anyone that we may provide your personal information. In addition, you expressly consent to be contacted in any manner including via email, direct mail, telephone or SMS text messaging, even if your information is listed on the US National Do Not Call registry or a similar registry. If you do not agree to these terms than do not use our site.
Finally, we may provide your personally identifiable information in accordance with the law, such as in response to a subpoena, warrant or other governmental request; if we believe it is necessary to protect our rights or the rights of any third party; in the event of a sale, merger, or acquisition; or if you consent to such disclosure.
Third-Party Hosting: We may contract with a third party to maintain and host the Website and to store data collected on the site. Therefore any information you submit, including personal information, may be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by a third-party host. You agree that Company is not liable for any breach of security due to the actions or inactions of the third-party host.
Links to Other Websites: The Website may contain links to other sites. Any such links are an accommodation to the respective third-party site owners and for your convenience. Sites linked to and from our Website are not necessarily under the control of Company, and Company shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any linked sites, or any link or linking program at any time. Please note that other sites will have their own privacy policies which may differ from this policy and once you enter another site their policy will control your use of that site. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any site that you visit.
Security: This Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Questions: If you have questions about this policy please contact us at .
Effective Date and Changes: This privacy policy is effective as of 9-1-10. We reserve the right to modify the terms of this privacy policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice on this page. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE FOLLOWING OUR POSTING OF A CHANGE NOTICE WILL CONSTITUTE BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THOSE CHANGES.
Let Us Know How We Can Help You
Contact Us
Call Today:
Phone:
503-699-5031
Email:
barbara@SpeakWellBeing.com
Address:
Portland, Oregon
Connect With Us
We look forward to connecting with you
If you are an event planner, put our expertise to work for you to connect you with a fabulous motivational keynote speaker for your conference or special event. Contact us now by phone or email for immediate assistance. If you are a speaker seeking representation, please include your website address, and video links with your inquiry.
Send Us A Message
Contact Us
Speaker Request Form
Event Reports, Speaker News, and Health Info
E-News Sign-Up
×
Send Us A Message
Name*
Your MessagePhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Copyright 2020 Speak Well Being
Designed & Created by Pegasus Online
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Planning for a Virtual Event? You're in the Right Place!Ideas for Virtual Events
